\documentclass[11pt]{article}
\usepackage[utf8]{inputenc}
\usepackage[margin=1in]{geometry}
\begin{document}

\centerline{\Huge \bf Alex Rivers}
\centerline{Email: alex.rivers@techly.ai}

\section*{Summary}
Experienced Senior Python Developer specializing in web development with a focus on FastAPI and React. Proven track record in architecting distributed systems and leading engineering teams to deliver high-performance solutions.

\section*{Strategic Skills}
\begin{itemize}
\item \textbf{FastAPI}: Extensive experience in building scalable web applications and APIs.
\end{itemize}

\section*{Professional Experience}
\begin{itemize}
\item \textbf{Senior Software Engineer at Quantum Dynamics}: Architected a distributed career ledger system using FastAPI. Implemented zero-hallucination guardrails for automated document synthesis and led a team of 5 engineers to deliver the v2 neural refinement engine. Utilized technologies including Python, FastAPI, Docker, and GCP.
\end{itemize}

\section*{Technical Projects}
\begin{itemize}
\item \textbf{NeuralNexus Chat Interface}: Developed a high-performance React chat component for real-time AI interactions, featuring LaTeX syntax highlighting and fact-checked synthesis. Utilized technologies such as React, Tailwind, Monaco Editor, and Socket.io.
\end{itemize}

\end{document}
